Yeah, I'm not even turning my desk light on for this one.
You're getting me in the scary campfire ghost story lighting right now because I've unleashed the demon inside here.
The gamer demon.
I have for a long time hung up the jersey when it came to grinding games competitively.
It's just not good for, not good for me. I get too into it and I'm too good at it.
Yeah, that's obviously me just joking around, but I get like very obsessive with like competing in a game.
So I haven't really competed in games since chess and before chess it was Apex Legends.
And it's been a few years now with no game that I really like laser focus on and try and get really good at until this last week with the finals.
I am hard addicted to the finals and I have been grinding the fuck out of it and I'm loving every second of it.
I'm sure you've seen a ton of videos I've been posting on my gaming channel, but I wanted to give you like a highlight reel of my ranked journey so far because man, I'm telling you I'm starting to be dangerous out there in the finals and it is amazing.
Let's land some huge winch clop. Oh my god, what a start.
I don't know the range.
Watch this read.
Damn.
Squad wipe.
Missed a lot of shots there. It didn't matter.
Boy.
Oh, that's unlucky.
There we go. I hunted that man down. I gave him no respite.
That wasn't a squad wipe so there's still one more. There he is.
Oh my god. I melted him.
I've wiped that team twice.
Oh, it's sad for guys.
I know they're pissed.
Whoa. Where they at?
I bet they're afraid to challenge this mountain now.
Put the fear of God and then.
Oh.
He's not going to challenge that again.
I got him again.
That team has got to be pissed.
Oh.
They are punching the air right now.
I've already got eight.
You love to see it. You really do.
We're all having a fun day on the finals.
Let's keep it going boys.
Okay.
Wow.
I still got the squad wipe.
Holy shit.
Oh my god. That was fucking dirty. What I just did to them.
Brother, they are all dead. You can just come rescue.
Did you not see him?
Oh, it was the same guy from last game.
There we go.
It's another wipe.
I'm leading the charge.
I've already got 10 kills.
It is crazy how hard I am clapping their cheeks right now.
This is a thing of beauty.
Oh, I almost had that.
I goomba stomped and I almost had that.
That would have been crazy.
Easy game.
15 stinkers in this one.
Gemini Christmas.
That was huge.
Through it off the map.
Where are they?
I've got him first.
Nice and easy.
Still in it up top fracking on the squad.
Oh shit.
Scary.
He's one. That's GG.
Nice. Nice.
I didn't get a lot of kills in that final round,
but I did a ton of damage in that final round, which is all that matters.
I left him really low for my team to finish off.
Made some easy strong plays. Easy dub.
Happy about that.
I'm just gonna bring this down.
I did not drop it. That's a shame.
Oh, the grenade got him though.
I just want to go over the navigation.
Brother, turn around. What are you doing?
Are you running right by you?
Holy shit. Did I just kill both of them with that?
I did.
Oh, and then I choked that.
Oh my god, that's strife.
Wait, where is he?
Oh nice. That was a wipe.
I'm going for it.
Sticking it.
Okay.
How did he spawn it?
I'm going for it.
Sticking it.
Ah.
He's low.
Nice. We got the cash out though.
Let's getting wiped there though, is actually almost a problem.
I didn't realize how much money you lose on that.
That was close.
Holy shit, that was close.
I had no idea. It was that much money you lose.
Let's take it.
Let's make like my nuts and hold them.
I got him.
That's too.
There we go.
Squad wipe.
Let's get it.
Yes sir, yes sir.
Final round in skeletal sniper with a squad wipe.
Is there anything that fits together more beautifully and more frequently?
Maybe peanut butter and jelly, but other than that, probably not much else.
God, that was clean.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, we got it. Holy fuck, that was a nail-biter.
Holy shit, that was a nail-biter.
Close call.
Oh, I would have been sad.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
No, how did you get it so quick?
How did you get it so quick?
I saw him the second he got on it.
He got it instantly.
Oh, we got it back.
Just all, just all, just all.
Oh, my God, just all, holy fuck.
No!
Yes, holy shit.
Clutch, I can't believe that.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
All right, well, we'll take it.
That's about as big of an ask-greaser as you can get.
24 and 10. Good enough.
Good enough.
That's a delivery.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Oh.
Pop it out.
This building would go in 30 seconds remaining.
Okay, scary.
I've got no dome, just got to rip it.
Just all, just all.
Nice.
Holy shit.
Come on, baby.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Dragging us, kicking and screaming into the qualification.
Yep.
Oh, yeah.
We only got two people on this squad.
We lost King Hero.
Can he just be replaced?
Can somebody else just take his place now, please?
This is so fucking silly, man.
This actually would have just been a freebie.
Like, he didn't even have to be good.
He just needed to have a pulse.
Like, he just needed to stay in the game.
That was so clean.
That was pink, bro.
Take it, take it.
Okay.
I'll do it all myself, then.
I don't even know you died.
All right, all right.
Yeah, that's okay.
I'm just shitting on him, though.
If we had a third, we could do this.
100% with a third, we do this for free.
Like, not just light in general, but I mean this weapon in particular feels really fast.
Here we go.
Okay, this feels pretty good.
Yep, that felt really fucking good.
Team wipe.
It's crazy.
How consistent I am at Team Wipes.
Holy fuck.
This is a brand new weapon for me, and I still wipe their whole ass.
Looking good.
What a shot.
He's low.
Brother, just turn and hit him once.
Oh, the man.
I'm in the jet setters in control.
Okay.
That was a headshot.
Two headshots.
Oh, I'm having a hard time hitting this guy, though.
Oh, my God.
That was dirty.
Holy fuck.
What I did to that guy was dirty, and I know he's mad about it.
I just saved my teammates ass with a crazy read.
Just lost another teammate.
Okay.
Man, finals at 2am is rough.
Finally, Jesus, that was having a hard time hitting that last shot.
Wait, we're already down to the line, man.
This is a fucking fun.
No, leave my teammate alone.
Can't you tell he's a pacifist?
Oh, lucky.
There we go.
Oh, that guy didn't miss his shots.
Damn, I thought I'd still have some more time there to just
pray on him.
That was sad, no.
He almost had it.
I got you.
I think we're cooked, though.
Regardless.
That's really good.
Okay.
All right.
I wiped him.
I don't see us winning this, but I'm definitely down to try.
Scary.
That's a squad wipe.
Oh.
No.
Damn.
If I didn't switch to grenades, I should have had more confidence.
I mean, it's once again, it's a completely wasted game because someone's left.
That guy was absolute trash and then rage quits as I'm raising him.
What?
Oh, that was so dirty.
Yikes, that was dirty.
He's pissed.
Oh, shoot me.
Oh.
Ugh.
Oh, fuck.
There's a different team.
Oh, I just killed my, oh, my cute and come out, fuck.
No.
No, I tried to de-mat that while I was sliding, but my de-materializer didn't come out.
Come on.
I really need a win.
I need a win.
It's been too long.
So many people leaving games just give me the win.
Ugh.
Good wipe.
Get away, get the vault.
Forget it.
Uh oh.
I'm getting a passage.
Prana, a mess of clear station safe.
Got him.
Squad wipe.
There we go.
Scary, scary.
Scary.
Nice.
Good shit.
Feels like we spawned so far away.
Just de-mat it down and we're gonna fight here.
We traded, we traded one for one, one for one.
One guy left, it's just a heavy on me.
Nice.
That's GG.
Let's go.
Ooh, that was close.
Finally.
That's what we needed.
Good shit.
That was close.
Alright.
I got real nervous when we lost that fight going in there.
20 and 13, not great, but it was good enough.
That's so good.
Oh, I didn't know where he was.
Oh, boy.
I've done all I can.
That looked pretty good.
Good.
Oh, can't reach that too short.
Where is that?
There we go.
There's the wipe.
This felt pretty good.
I like this weapon.
This gun is nice.
Oh, that gun's much better for that range.
There we go.
I'm liking this round.
This is feeling good.
Plenty of time.
Nice.
I fucking knew I could get the rez off and take this back.
Yeah, I'm really getting the hang of this now.
I'm just going to play light.
I think that's just the move.
I can do some serious carrying his light.
Oh.
Luch.
I almost turned that too.
I just saved us so fucking hard.
Holy shit.
Jesus.
Okay.
Give myself a round of applause.
I'd love to see it.
Only care about pink.
Oh, God.
Oh, I tried the low profile.
That's fine.
I got pink.
Okay.
I put the team on my back hard there.
God, I was working.
I was working.
No.
Almost, almost, almost.
I was skating around him there.
Protect me.
Do you have a bubble?
Bubble, bubble, bubble, bubble, bubble.
Holy shit.
I can't see him.
Nice.
I got it.
Okay.
Now we're never.
Anyway, anyway.
Yeah, I don't lose those.
Where's the squad?
There we go.
This is one guy.
All right.
Did it all myself.
All three.
All by my lonesome.
I will drag us kicking and screaming to a win if I have to.
Whoo.
Got him.
Oh, now that was actually dirty.
That was actually dirty.
So got all three there.
What?
How did they get it?
All right.
Whoo.
Baby.
I hunted that man down.
Scared him.
I'm going crazy.
Oh, I'm going crazy.
Got you.
13 kills.
I got my shit mixed up there.
Where is the other guy?
17 kills.
17 kills right now.
I am wiping their ass.
Holy shit.
Wow.
Okay.
He's throwing knives.
These throwing knives.
I don't know where that was.
Got one.
Got two.
All three, baby.
That's a solo team wipe.
Give me that shit.
I want to catch this bitch out.
What a fucking shame.
We had that.
We should have had that.
I was going so crazy.
35.
I dropped 35 on him.